<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>george.entenman.name</title>
    <description>Collecting my thoughts in one place</description>
    <link>/</link>
    <atom:link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Guymon, Oklahoma</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Today we drove &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.google.com/maps/dir/Tulsa,+OK/Enid,+OK/Guymon,+OK/@36.4047352,-99.8390025,8z/data=!3m1!4b1!4m20!4m19!1m5!1m1!1s0x87b692b8ddd12e8f:0xe76910c81bd96af7!2m2!1d-95.992775!2d36.1539816!1m5!1m1!1s0x87afd4ecadc8ee41:0xd3c0cc0fc8aba39a!2m2!1d-97.8783911!2d36.3955891!1m5!1m1!1s0x870628e0e00b2d4d:0x505b9998f65d1715!2m2!1d-101.4815493!2d36.6828041!3e0&quot;&gt;from Tulsa to Guymon, OK&lt;/a&gt;. It was approximately 326 generally flat, straight miles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;we-had-a-very-nice-bb-in-tulsa&quot;&gt;We had a very nice B&amp;amp;B in Tulsa&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was a short drive from the Philbrook Museum.  It was quiet and cute.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/2014_bigtrip/2014_07_11_Guymon_Oklahoma/mackintosh_inn.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Mackintosh Inn&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;it-was-a-pretty-drive-once-we-got-through-the-detours-in-tulsa&quot;&gt;It was a pretty drive once we got through the detours in Tulsa.&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The AAA triptik didn’t seem to know about the detour only 4 miles from their office!  Fortunately, my sense of direction and Iris’ map-reading got us back on the road.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It wasn’t long before we started seeing oil rigs pumping slowly away.  The land alternated between rolling hills and flat plains.  There were long spaces between moments of “civilization”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/2014_bigtrip/2014_07_11_Guymon_Oklahoma/Highway_412.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;XXX&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;first-mesas&quot;&gt;First Mesas&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m looking forward to a lot more…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/2014_bigtrip/2014_07_11_Guymon_Oklahoma/first_mesas.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;XXX&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;prison-town&quot;&gt;Prison Town&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This town had little more than a prison.  Driving into town, we were greeted by a sign saying &lt;strong&gt;Hitchikers may be escaped prisoners&lt;/strong&gt;!!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/2014_bigtrip/2014_07_11_Guymon_Oklahoma/prison.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;XXX&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;yer-iconic-western-scene&quot;&gt;Yer iconic Western scene&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/2014_bigtrip/2014_07_11_Guymon_Oklahoma/gas_station.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;XXX&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;guymon&quot;&gt;Guymon&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are in the &lt;strong&gt;Comfort Inn&lt;/strong&gt; in Guymon.  We walked to a steakhouse next door for delicious steaks.  Now we’re holed up for the night. Tomorrow: Raton, New Mexico.  Why would you name a town “Rat”?  Better than “Rat Mouth” (Boca Raton), I suppose.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2014 16:46:22 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>/misc/2014-07-11-we-made-it-to-guymon-oklahoma.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/misc/2014-07-11-we-made-it-to-guymon-oklahoma.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Tulsa, Oklahoma</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;We had a relatively short drive today from Fayetteville, AR, to Tulsa OK.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before leaving, we took a quick driving tour of the Univ of Arkansas campus and extremely quaint college street.  We also visited the downtown square, where there was a farmers’ market.  Fayetteville turned out to be a hilly, town with old buildings, many restored, with lots of trees and interesting houses.  We wondered where our friend Celisa Steele had lived.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When we crossed the Oklahoma border, we discovered why North Carolina gets away with calling itself the “good roads state”.  Guess there are so many conservatives here that they’d rather spend money repairing their cars than building good roads.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;now-we-are-ready-for-the-panhandle&quot;&gt;Now we are ready for the Panhandle!&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Eventually we got to Tulsa and went first to the local VW dealer to buy a special plastic funnel that will enable us to use diesel pumps that haven’t been modified for newer cars.  We got very worried in Virginia where we found three stations with diesel that we couldn’t put into our tank.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When we walked out of the VW Parts Dept with the gizmo and stood by our car, a salesman came out intending to sell us the beautiful Passat we were standing next to.  He couldn’t figure out why he didn’t see the expected stickers.  It was funny when we told him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/2014_bigtrip/2014_07_10_Tulsa/vw_dealer.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;VW diesel gizmo&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-philbrook-museum&quot;&gt;The Philbrook Museum&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Parts of Tulsa are incredibly rich and nice.  This is due, of course, to the oil boom here in the last century.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We went to the Philbrook Museum, which is housed in a rich family’s former mansion.  It was a beautiful museum with a good collection.  We saw a small special exhibition of Manet.  Manet apparently invented the idea of doing &lt;strong&gt;series&lt;/strong&gt; of painting of the same scene as it changed over time.  My theory of art is that if you make one object, it is an object, but if you obsessively make lots of them, it is art.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The museum had a lot of Southwestern Native art and beautiful gardens that we weren’t supposed to walk in because it threatened to continue raining.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/2014_bigtrip/2014_07_10_Tulsa/crows.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;XXX&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/2014_bigtrip/2014_07_10_Tulsa/gardens.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;XXX&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-philbrook-downtown-museum&quot;&gt;The Philbrook Downtown Museum&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We drove to an industrial area just north of downtown Tulsa to see a smaller museum devoted mostely to Southwest Native art.  While asking with the people at the front desk about places to eat, they gave me a brochure.  When I noticed that we were near a &lt;strong&gt;John Hope Franklin&lt;/strong&gt; park, they told me that we were in the &lt;strong&gt;Black Wall Street&lt;/strong&gt; area where the terrible race riot of 1921 took place.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;dinner&quot;&gt;Dinner&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We asked the advice of a very nice man smoking outside his store for a place to get good craft beer as well as food, and he recommended &lt;em&gt;The Tavern&lt;/em&gt; on a corner nearby.  We sat in a window table and had a dinner that was much better than the one in the &lt;strong&gt;Chrystal Springs&lt;/strong&gt; restaurant!  It was very, very good.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/2014_bigtrip/2014_07_10_Tulsa/iris.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;XXX&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/2014_bigtrip/2014_07_10_Tulsa/the_tavern.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;XXX&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;tulsa-drillers&quot;&gt;Tulsa Drillers&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For one inning we watched the &lt;strong&gt;Tulsa Drillers&lt;/strong&gt; play a baseball team from Arkansas.  It was fun.  Not the Durham Bulls, you understand, but fun.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/2014_bigtrip/2014_07_10_Tulsa/tulsa_drillers.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;XXX&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;black-wall-street&quot;&gt;Black Wall Street&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There was not much - actually nothing but a street sign - to indicate that this area had once been a thriving African American community.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/2014_bigtrip/2014_07_10_Tulsa/black_wall_street.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;XXX&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2014 17:59:15 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>/misc/2014-07-10-tulsa-oklahoma.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/misc/2014-07-10-tulsa-oklahoma.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fayetteville, Arkansas</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;We headed towards Fayetteville, AR, and discovered Bentonville.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;heading-west-from-blytheville-ar&quot;&gt;Heading West from Blytheville, AR&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We took the straightest path possible from Blytheville towards Fayetteville.  Thank goodness we didn’t follow our original plan of going all the way to Tulsa, OK.  Today was a pretty long drive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We started out through endless miles of perfectly flat agricultural land.  Here’s one of the few photos I took - photos simply wouldn’t capture the openness and endlessness of this place.  Can you spot the crop duster at the bottom right of the photo?  It came a lot closer but I didn’t get a better photo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/2014_bigtrip/2014-07-10-fayetteville-arkansas/01_crop_duster.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;XXX&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-ozarks&quot;&gt;The Ozarks&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think that they consider the Ozarks to be mountains.  Now I realize that this must be because they’d just ridden through the same totally flat country we had.  The Ozarks that we saw were barely hills.  The area reminded me of Southern Virginia near Hillsville. It was pretty and peaceful.  It looks like a place to stop and relax and enjoy the air and breeze.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/2014_bigtrip/2014-07-10-fayetteville-arkansas/02_Ozarks.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Ozarks&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/2014_bigtrip/2014-07-10-fayetteville-arkansas/03_Ozarks.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Ozarks&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/2014_bigtrip/2014-07-10-fayetteville-arkansas/04_Ozarks.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Ozarks&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the advice of an Arkansas Transportation Dept worker I talked to at a rest stop, we searched out Fred’s Fish Restaurant near &lt;strong&gt;Mountain Home, AR&lt;/strong&gt;.  We enjoyed our fried catfish and wonderful view.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/2014_bigtrip/2014-07-10-fayetteville-arkansas/05_Ozarks.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Fish restaurant&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/2014_bigtrip/2014-07-10-fayetteville-arkansas/06_Ozarks.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Fish restaurant&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;its-worth-asking-for-information-at-rest-stops&quot;&gt;It’s worth asking for information at rest stops.&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We stopped about an hour and a half outside of Fayetteville, we stopped at a rest stop so that Iris could take the wheel again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We went into a little tourist information office there and were welcomed by very helpful people.  During our conversation, they mentioned &lt;strong&gt;Bentonville&lt;/strong&gt;, the town where Walmart is headquartered.  Apparently a lot of the money that they’ve sucked out of the rest of America has been send in Bentonville.  One of the Walton heirs in particular has built an amazing museum, the &lt;strong&gt;Chrystal Bridges Museum of American Art&lt;/strong&gt;.  Bentonville turns out to be a hairy 30-minute race up a curvy freeway from Fayetteville, but it was very well worth the drive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The museum is beautiful.  I loved the collection.  Iris found it a but unfocussed, probably because it had been put together too recently to be able to buy everything needed for completeness.  The museum is relatively small, so you can see the collection in a short amount of time.  The staff is &lt;strong&gt;very&lt;/strong&gt; enthusiastic - the people patrolling the galleries love to talk - it’s not New York.  The art was beautiful and the experience enjoyable.  And the museum itself is spectacular.  I wish we’d had time to explore the grounds outside, where they have more art, but we got there too late to do everything.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We had a quiet dinner inside one of the bridges and then got back on the racetrack back to Fayetteville and our motel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/2014_bigtrip/2014-07-10-fayetteville-arkansas/07_Bentonville.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Museum&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/2014_bigtrip/2014-07-10-fayetteville-arkansas/08_Bentonville.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Museum&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/2014_bigtrip/2014-07-10-fayetteville-arkansas/09_Bentonville.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Museum&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/2014_bigtrip/2014-07-10-fayetteville-arkansas/10_Bentonville.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Museum&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/2014_bigtrip/2014-07-10-fayetteville-arkansas/11_Bentonville.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Museum&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/2014_bigtrip/2014-07-10-fayetteville-arkansas/12_Bentonville.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Museum&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/2014_bigtrip/2014-07-10-fayetteville-arkansas/13_Bentonville.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Museum&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/2014_bigtrip/2014-07-10-fayetteville-arkansas/14_Bentonville.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Museum&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/2014_bigtrip/2014-07-10-fayetteville-arkansas/15_Bentonville.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Museum&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/2014_bigtrip/2014-07-10-fayetteville-arkansas/16_Bentonville.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Museum&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/2014_bigtrip/2014-07-10-fayetteville-arkansas/17_Bentonville.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Museum&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/2014_bigtrip/2014-07-10-fayetteville-arkansas/18_Bentonville.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Museum&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/2014_bigtrip/2014-07-10-fayetteville-arkansas/19_Bentonville.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Museum&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/2014_bigtrip/2014-07-10-fayetteville-arkansas/20_Bentonville.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Museum&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/2014_bigtrip/2014-07-10-fayetteville-arkansas/21_Bentonville.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Museum&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2014 02:59:18 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>/misc/2014-07-10-fayetteville-arkansas.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/misc/2014-07-10-fayetteville-arkansas.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Blytheville, AR</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;We made it to Blytheville, AR, one day ahead of schedule.  This will make the drive to Tulsa a lot more manageable since we can now do it in two stages.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;that-bookstore-in-blytheville&quot;&gt;That Bookstore in Blytheville&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We first went to the bookstore that David Perry had told us to visit.  We stayed almost an hour and would have loved to stay longer.  Mr Crawley, the owner, is wonderfully engaging and a terrific salesman!  Guess I’ll find out if I like John Grisham!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/2014_07_08_don_and_lori_and_kody/that_bookstore.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;That Bookstore&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/2014_07_08_don_and_lori_and_kody/chris_crawley.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Chris Crawley&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;georges-brother-don-and-his-family&quot;&gt;George’s Brother Don and his family&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We had a fabulous time with Don, Lori and their grandson Kody.  We had never met Lori or Kody before and found that we like them &lt;strong&gt;very&lt;/strong&gt;  much!  Brother Don did well!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;brothers&quot;&gt;Brothers&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/2014_07_08_don_and_lori_and_kody/don_lynn.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Don and George&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;don-lori-and-kody&quot;&gt;Don, Lori and Kody&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/2014_07_08_don_and_lori_and_kody/don_kody_lori.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Don, Lori, Kody&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/2014_07_08_don_and_lori_and_kody/kody_lori.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Kody and Lori&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/2014_07_08_don_and_lori_and_kody/lori_don.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Lori and Don&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2014 18:55:59 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>/misc/2014-07-08-blytheville-ar.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/misc/2014-07-08-blytheville-ar.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>First day on the road to the west</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;We’re underway!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;we-left-at-1008am-this-morning&quot;&gt;We left at 10:08am this morning.&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This felt like a miracle!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are now in a Quality Inn in Lebanon, TN, about 30 miles from Nashville.  Tomorrow we might actually make it to Blytheville, AR, where my brother Don lives.  I thought it would take us another day, but it might not.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.google.com/maps/dir/Chapel+Hill,+NC/Wytheville,+VA/Lebanon,+TN/@36.3292786,-87.088224,6z/data=!3m1!4b1!4m20!4m19!1m5!1m1!1s0x89acc31c216e7ea7:0x7f03bae00443e4cb!2m2!1d-79.0558445!2d35.9131996!1m5!1m1!1s0x8851e036ed078515:0xa66a3b265ddc58d!2m2!1d-81.084811!2d36.9484528!1m5!1m1!1s0x8864047f38949553:0x43a1e19aa090111a!2m2!1d-86.2911024!2d36.2081098!3e0&quot;&gt;Google maps&lt;/a&gt; says that we drove 497 miles today.  I’ll check the odometer tomorrow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We alternated driving.  Iris slept pretty well when I was driving but I didn’t sleep much when it was her turn to drive.  But I did okay.  I’m happy with our first day’s progress.  Kudos to David Perry for telling me both what route to take and how far to shoot for on our first day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’d take a photo and post it.  But you know what?  You’d have no idea where we were - this place looks like everywhere else in Americar.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2014 17:28:12 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>/misc/2014-07-07-first-day-on-the-road-to-the-west.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/misc/2014-07-07-first-day-on-the-road-to-the-west.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Dinner at the Andersons</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Iris and I went to the Andersons for a wonderful dinner.  Barbara’s friend Beth was visiting.  She has to come to the US from Israel several times a year to take care of her mother in Waco.  It was wonderful seeing Beth again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;playing-with-my-new-camera&quot;&gt;Playing with my new camera.&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m sorry I didn’t get good photos of everyone.  I’ve got to get a photo of John next time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;beth&quot;&gt;Beth&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/2014-07-06-dinner-at-the-andersons/Beth2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Beth&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/2014-07-06-dinner-at-the-andersons/Beth.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Beth&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;barbara-and-heidi&quot;&gt;Barbara and Heidi&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/2014-07-06-dinner-at-the-andersons/barbara_and_heidi.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Barbara and Heidi&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;david&quot;&gt;David&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/2014-07-06-dinner-at-the-andersons/david.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;David&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;luke&quot;&gt;Luke&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/2014-07-06-dinner-at-the-andersons/luke.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Luke&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;martin&quot;&gt;Martin&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/2014-07-06-dinner-at-the-andersons/martin.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Martin&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/2014-07-06-dinner-at-the-andersons/martin_as_tintin.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Martin as Tintin&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;rob&quot;&gt;Rob&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/2014-07-06-dinner-at-the-andersons/rob.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Rob&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2014 14:58:38 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>/misc/2014-07-06-dinner-at-the-andersons.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/misc/2014-07-06-dinner-at-the-andersons.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>4th of July with Jane and James</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Thanks to Jane and James for yet another wonderful &lt;strong&gt;4th of July&lt;/strong&gt; party.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These are the photos that came out the best.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;art&quot;&gt;Art&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/2014_07_04_Protzman_Brown/2014-07-04-resized-Art.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Art&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;brenda&quot;&gt;Brenda&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/2014_07_04_Protzman_Brown/2014-07-04-resized-Brenda.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Brenda&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;diana&quot;&gt;Diana&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/2014_07_04_Protzman_Brown/2014-07-04-resized-Diana.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Diana&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;fritzi&quot;&gt;Fritzi&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/2014_07_04_Protzman_Brown/2014-07-04-resized-Fritzi.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Fritzi&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;jane&quot;&gt;Jane&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/2014_07_04_Protzman_Brown/2014-07-04-resized-Jane.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Jane&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;lily&quot;&gt;Lily&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/2014_07_04_Protzman_Brown/2014-07-04-resized-Lily-2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Lily&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/2014_07_04_Protzman_Brown/2014-07-04-resized-Lily.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Lily&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;linda-carol&quot;&gt;Linda Carol&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/2014_07_04_Protzman_Brown/2014-07-04-resized-LindaCarol.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Linda Carol&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;margaret&quot;&gt;Margaret&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/2014_07_04_Protzman_Brown/2014-07-04-resized-Margaret.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Margaret&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;martha&quot;&gt;Martha&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/2014_07_04_Protzman_Brown/2014-07-04-resized-Martha.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Martha&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;matt&quot;&gt;Matt&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/2014_07_04_Protzman_Brown/2014-07-04-resized-Matt.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Matt&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;norm&quot;&gt;Norm&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/2014_07_04_Protzman_Brown/2014-07-04-resized-Norm.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Norm&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;steve&quot;&gt;Steve&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/2014_07_04_Protzman_Brown/2014-07-04-resized-Steve.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Steve&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2014 17:34:20 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>/misc/2014-07-04-4th-of-july-with-jane-and-james.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/misc/2014-07-04-4th-of-july-with-jane-and-james.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A restaurant to entice Becca and Warner to visit NC</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Iris and I went to Hillsborough yesterday to vote early.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Afterwards, we went to &lt;a href=&quot;http://laplacehillsborough.com/&quot;&gt;LaPlace&lt;/a&gt;, a cute restaurant on Churton Street and had lunch at the bar.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;enticements&quot;&gt;Enticements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When Iris dug her fork into this cake, she immediately said, “We have to bring Becca and Warner here!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/2014-07-04-a-restaurant-to-entice-becca-and-warner-to-visit/LaplaceRestaurant.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;The cake&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;LaPlace&lt;/strong&gt;’s speciality should appeal to Warner:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/2014-07-04-a-restaurant-to-entice-becca-and-warner-to-visit/LaplaceRestaurant2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Sausage&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2014 07:34:59 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>/misc/2014-07-04-a-restaurant-to-entice-becca-and-warner-to-visit.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/misc/2014-07-04-a-restaurant-to-entice-becca-and-warner-to-visit.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Triolet</title>
        <description>
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2014 20:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>/idproject/2014/06/20/triolet.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/idproject/2014/06/20/triolet.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Near Crooked Creek</title>
        <description>
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2014 20:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>/idproject/2014/06/20/near-crooked-creek.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/idproject/2014/06/20/near-crooked-creek.html</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
